    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Omag</Title>
      <Ability>Between any of the Phases, you may discard this card to remove a Disabled Upgrade Token from 1 of your [WEAPON] Upgrades. OR When attacking, during the Declare Target step, you may discard this card to target a ship at Range 1-3. Choose 1 non-Borg [WEAPON] Upgrade on the target ship with a printed cost of 4 or less and disable it to perform its attack as if it were deployed to your ship.</Ability>
      <Unique>Y</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Crew</Type>
      <Faction>Ferengi</Faction>
      <Cost>5</Cost>
      <Id>omag_72221j</Id>
      <Set>72221j</Set>
      <Special></Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Geodesic Pulse</Title>
      <Ability>ACTION: Immediately perform an additional maneuver with a speed of 2 or less. You do not lose your Perform Action step if your ship's base overlaps another ship's base with this maneuver. In addition, you do not suffer any damage from Obstacles. You cannot attack this round.</Ability>
      <Unique>N</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Tech</Type>
      <Faction>Ferengi</Faction>
      <Cost>5</Cost>
      <Id>geodesic_pulse_72221j</Id>
      <Set>72221j</Set>
      <Special></Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Kidnap</Title>
      <Ability>ACTION: Disable all of your remaining Shields and target a ship at Rnage 1-2 that is not cloaked and has no Active Shields. Discard this card to steal 1 [CREW] Upgrade on the target ship. If the stolen Upgrade exceeds your ship's restrictions, discard that Upgrade instead of stealing it. This Upgrade may only be purchased for a Ferengi Captain assigned to a Ferengi ship.</Ability>
      <Unique>Y</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Talent</Type>
      <Faction>Ferengi</Faction>
      <Cost>5</Cost>
      <Id>kidnap_72221j</Id>
      <Set>72221j</Set>
      <Special>OnlyFerengiCaptainFerengiShip</Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Weapon Ports</Title>
      <Ability>ATTACK: Disable this card to perform this attack. While this card is disabled, you roll 1 less defense die. If you hit an Attack Squadron with this attack, during the Deal Damage step, discard 1 Attack Squadron Token for each uncanceled [HIT] or [CRIT] result (max 3). You may only fire this weapon fro your forward firing arc.</Ability>
      <Unique>N</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack>4</Attack>
      <Range>1-3</Range>
      <Type>Weapon</Type>
      <Faction>Ferengi</Faction>
      <Cost>4</Cost>
      <Id>weapon_ports_72221j</Id>
      <Set>72221j</Set>
      <Special></Special>
    </Upgrade>
