    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Mutli-adaptive Shields</Title>
      <Ability>This upgrade only functions while you have Active Shields. Each time you defend, roll +1 defense die. When defending, you roll your full defense dice in spite of the presence of an enemy ship's [SCAN] token. In addition, you roll your full defense against any Minefield Tokens. This Upgrade may only be purchased for a Federation ship.</Ability>
      <Unique>Y</Unique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Tech</Type>
      <Faction>Federation</Faction>
      <Cost>5</Cost>
      <Id>mutli_adaptive_shields_71509</Id>
      <Set>71509</Set>
      <Special>OnlyFederationShip</Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Reinforced Structural Integrity</Title>
      <Ability>Each time your ship takes damage, place 1 of the damage cards that your ship receives beneath this card. All excess damage affects the ship as normal. You cannot place critical damage cards beneath this card. Once there are 3 damage cards beneath this card, discard this Upgrade and all cards beneath it. This Upgrade costs +5 SP for any ship other than the U.S.S. Raven.</Ability>
      <Unique>Y</Unique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Tech</Type>
      <Faction>Federation</Faction>
      <Cost>5</Cost>
      <Id>reinforced_structural_integrity_71509</Id>
      <Set>71509</Set>
      <Special></Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Research Mission</Title>
      <Ability>During the Roll Defense Dice step of the Combat Phase, you may disable this card to roll +1 defense die.</Ability>
      <Unique>N</Unique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Talent</Type>
      <Faction>Independent</Faction>
      <Cost>2</Cost>
      <Id>research_mission_71509</Id>
      <Set>71509</Set>
      <Special></Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Erin Hansen</Title>
      <Ability>During the Planning Phase, after all ships have chosen their Maneuvers, you may discard this card to target one enemy ship at Range 1-3 and look at that ship's chosen Maneuver. You may then change your Maneuver. The target ship cannot change its Maneuver after you look at it.</Ability>
      <Unique>Y</Unique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Crew</Type>
      <Faction>Independent</Faction>
      <Cost>3</Cost>
      <Id>erin_hansen_71509</Id>
      <Set>71509</Set>
      <Special></Special>
    </Upgrade>
