    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Klingon Stealth Team</Title>
      <Ability>ACTION: Discard this card to target a ship at Range 2-3 that is not Cloaked. Disable 1 [TECH] or [WEAPON] Upgrade of your choice on target ship and then discard 1 [CREW] Upgrade of your choice on that ship, if possible. This Upgrade may only be purchased for a Klingon ship and no ship may be equipped with more than one Klingon Stealth Team Upgrade.</Ability>
      <Unique>N</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Crew</Type>
      <Faction>Klingon</Faction>
      <Cost>5</Cost>
      <Id>klingon_stealth_team_71999p</Id>
      <Set>71999p</Set>
      <Special>NoMoreThanOnePerShipKlingon</Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Cloaked Mines</Title>
      <Ability>During the Planning Phase, you may discard this card to place a Minefield Token within Range 1 of your ship (in any direction), but not within Range 3 of an enemy ship. If an enemy ship passes within Range 1 of the token, roll 3 attack dice (-1 if the target ship immediately performs a [SCAN] Action). Any [HIT] or [CRIT] damage the target ship as normal. The affected ship does not roll any defense dice.</Ability>
      <Unique>N</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Tech</Type>
      <Faction>Klingon</Faction>
      <Cost>3</Cost>
      <Id>cloaked_mines_71999p</Id>
      <Set>71999p</Set>
      <Special></Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Mauk-to'Vor</Title>
      <Ability>ACTION: Discard this card and your Captain Card to gain a number of attack dice for your first attack this round equal to 1/2 of that Captain's Skill number, rounded down (max +3). Place an Auxiliary Power Token beside your ship. You cannot perform any free Actions this round. This Upgrade may only be purchased for a Klingon Captain assigned to a Klingon ship.</Ability>
      <Unique>Y</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Talent</Type>
      <Faction>Klingon</Faction>
      <Cost>5</Cost>
      <Id>mauk_to_vor_71999p</Id>
      <Set>71999p</Set>
      <Special></Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Ambush Attack</Title>
      <Ability>ATTACK: Discard this card to perform this attack. If your ship is cloaked, gain +1 attack die for this attack. If your ship is not in the target ship's forward or rear firing arcs, you may convert all of your [BATTLESTATIONS] results into [HIT] results. No ship may be equipped with more than one Ambush Attack Upgrade.</Ability>
      <Unique>N</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack>5</Attack>
      <Range>1-2</Range>
      <Type>Weapon</Type>
      <Faction>Klingon</Faction>
      <Cost>5</Cost>
      <Id>ambush_attack_71999p</Id>
      <Set>71999p</Set>
      <Special>NoMoreThanOnePerShip</Special>
    </Upgrade>
