    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Karden</Title>
      <Ability>ACTION: Disable this card to gain +2 attack dice and roll -2 defense dice this round. This Upgrade may only be purchased for a Kazon ship.</Ability>
      <Unique>Y</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Crew</Type>
      <Faction>Kazon</Faction>
      <Cost>3</Cost>
      <Id>karden_71793</Id>
      <Set>71793</Set>
      <Special>Yes</Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Haliz</Title>
      <Ability>When defending, during the Declare Target step, you my remove your Captain Card from the game to cancel that attack. If you do this, the attacking ship cannot perform another attack during that round. This card then becomes your Captain Card with a skill of 3. This Upgrade may only be purchased for a Kazon ship.</Ability>
      <Unique>Y</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Crew</Type>
      <Faction>Kazon</Faction>
      <Cost>4</Cost>
      <Id>haliz_71793</Id>
      <Set>71793</Set>
      <Special>Yes</Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Tractor Beam</Title>
      <Ability>During the Activation Phase, when a ship within Range 1 of your ship reveals a Maneuver with a number of 3 or higher, before that ship moves, you may discard this card to subtract 2 from that Maneuver's number. No ship may be equipped with more than 1 of this Upgrade.</Ability>
      <Unique>N</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Tech</Type>
      <Faction>Kazon</Faction>
      <Cost>2</Cost>
      <Id>tractor_beam_71793</Id>
      <Set>71793</Set>
      <Special>Yes</Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>First Maje</Title>
      <Ability>This Upgrade does not require an Upgrade slot and may only be equipped to a Kazon ship with a Kazon Captain. While this Upgrade is equipped to your ship, you gain 1 additional [TECH] Upgrade slot to your Upgrade Bar and your Captain Skill increases by 2. During the Planning Phase, you may discard this card to target a ship at Range 1. Disable 1 [TECH] Upgrade on the target ship and then steal it, even if it exceeds your ship's restrictions.</Ability>
      <Unique>Y</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Talent</Type>
      <Faction>Kazon</Faction>
      <Cost>5</Cost>
      <Id>first_maje_71793</Id>
      <Set>71793</Set>
      <Special>Yes</Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Particle Beam Weapon</Title>
      <Ability>ATTACK: Disable this card to perform this attack. You may fire this weapon from your forward or rear firing arcs.</Ability>
      <Unique>N</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack>5</Attack>
      <Range>1-2</Range>
      <Type>Weapon</Type>
      <Faction>Kazon</Faction>
      <Cost>4</Cost>
      <Id>particle_beam_weapon_71793</Id>
      <Set>71793</Set>
      <Special></Special>
    </Upgrade>
