    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Sirna Kolrami</Title>
      <Ability>When defending, during the Compare Results step, if you cancel all of your opponent's [HIT] and [CRIT] results, you may discard this card and disable 1 of your other Upgrades to immediately roll a number of attack dice equal to the number of [HIT] or [CRIT] results that were cancelled (max 4 dice). The attacking ship suffers normal damage for every [HIT] or [CRIT] result you roll with these dice.</Ability>
      <Unique>Y</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Crew</Type>
      <Faction>Federation</Faction>
      <Cost>5</Cost>
      <Id>sirna_kolrami_71997p</Id>
      <Set>71997p</Set>
      <Special></Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Computer Analysis</Title>
      <Ability>During the Planning Phase, you may discard this card to remove all the Disabled Upgrade Tokens from all of your other Upgrades.</Ability>
      <Unique>Y</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Talent</Type>
      <Faction>Federation</Faction>
      <Cost>4</Cost>
      <Id>computer_analysis_71997p</Id>
      <Set>71997p</Set>
      <Special></Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Escape Transporter</Title>
      <Ability>When your ship is destroyed, before removing it from the play area, you may discard this card to target a friendly ship at Range 1-2 that is not cloaked and disable all of that ship's remaining Shields. Select up to 3 other Upgrades that were deployed to this ship and redeploy them to the target ship, even if it exceeds that ship's restrictions. If any of the redeployed Upgrades were already disabled, they remain disabled. This Upgrade may only be purchased for a Federation Shuttlecraft.</Ability>
      <Unique>N</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Tech</Type>
      <Faction>Federation</Faction>
      <Cost>2</Cost>
      <Id>escape_transporter_71997p</Id>
      <Set>71997p</Set>
      <Special>OnlyShipClass_Type_7_Shuttlecraft</Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Warp Drive</Title>
      <Ability>During the Activation Phase, if you reveal a 2 [STRAIGHT] Maneuver, you may disable this card to perform a white 3 [STRAIGHT] or a red 4 [STRAIGHT] Maneuver instead. This Upgrade may only be purchased for a Federation Shuttlecraft and no ship may be equipped with more than 1 "Warp Drive" Upgrade.</Ability>
      <Unique>N</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Tech</Type>
      <Faction>Federation</Faction>
      <Cost>2</Cost>
      <Id>warp_drive_71997p</Id>
      <Set>71997p</Set>
      <Special>NoMoreThanOnePerShip</Special>
    </Upgrade>
