    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Ro Laren</Title>
      <Ability>When attacking, during the Roll Attack Dice step, you may discard this card to roll +2 attack dice for that attack. In addition, if this Upgrade is deployed to a Bajoran ship, during the Modify Attack Dice step, you may re-roll all of your [BATTLESTATIONS] results for that attack. This Upgrade may only be purchased for a Bajoran or Federation ship.</Ability>
      <Unique>Y</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Crew</Type>
      <Faction>Bajoran</Faction>
      <Cost>5</Cost>
      <Id>ro_laren_72221g</Id>
      <Set>72221g</Set>
      <Special>OnlyBajoranFederation</Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Pursuit</Title>
      <Ability>When attacking a ship that you already have target locked, during the Roll Attack Dice step, you may discard this card to roll +2 attack dice. This Upgrade may only be purchased for a ship with a Hull value of 3 or less.</Ability>
      <Unique>Y</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Talent</Type>
      <Faction>Bajoran</Faction>
      <Cost>5</Cost>
      <Id>pursuit_72221g</Id>
      <Set>72221g</Set>
      <Special>OnlyHull3OrLess</Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Navigational Sensors</Title>
      <Ability>After performing a Come About Maneuver, you may disable this card to immediately perform an additional maneuver. This Upgrade may only be purchased for a Bajoran Interceptor and no ship may be equipped with more than 1 "Navigational Sensors" Upgrade.</Ability>
      <Unique>N</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Tech</Type>
      <Faction>Bajoran</Faction>
      <Cost>5</Cost>
      <Id>navigational_sensors_72221g</Id>
      <Set>72221g</Set>
      <Special>NoMoreThanOnePerShipBajoranInterceptor</Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Phaser Strike</Title>
      <Ability>ACTION: During the Combat Phase, you may attack with this Weapon as if you had a Captain Skill of "10". ATTACK: Disable this card to perform this attack. Range combat bonuses apply to this attack. This Upgrade may only be purchased for a ship with a Hull value of 3 or less and costs +5 SP for any ship other than a Bajoran Interceptor.</Ability>
      <Unique>N</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack>4</Attack>
      <Range>1-3</Range>
      <Type>Weapon</Type>
      <Faction>Bajoran</Faction>
      <Cost>5</Cost>
      <Id>phaser_strike_72221g</Id>
      <Set>72221g</Set>
      <Special>PhaserStrike</Special>
    </Upgrade>
