    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Ibix Dynasty</Title>
      <Ability>Add 2 [WEAPON] Upgrade slots to your Upgrade Bar. If this card is discarded, your ship loses these Upgrade slots. When defending, before any dice are rolled, you may discard this card and 1 of your [WEAPON] Upgrades to cancel the attack.</Ability>
      <Unique>Y</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Talent</Type>
      <Faction>Xindi</Faction>
      <Cost>5</Cost>
      <Id>ibix_dynasty_72004p</Id>
      <Set>72004p</Set>
      <Special>AddTwoWeaponSlots</Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Aquatic Councilor</Title>
      <Ability>When defending, during the Roll Defense Dice step, you may disable this card to roll 1 additional defense die. OR When defending, during the Roll Defense Dice step, you may discard this card to roll 2 additional defense dice.</Ability>
      <Unique>N</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Crew</Type>
      <Faction>Xindi</Faction>
      <Cost>5</Cost>
      <Id>aquatic_councilor_72004p</Id>
      <Set>72004p</Set>
      <Special></Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Escape Pod</Title>
      <Ability>Whenever one of your [CREW] Upgrades is supposed to be discarded, you may place that Upgrade beneath this card instead. While and Upgrade is beneath this card it cannot be targeted or used in any way. If your ship is destroyed, you may remove the [CREW] Upgrade from beneath this card and deploy it to a friendly ship within Range 1-3 of your ship.</Ability>
      <Unique>N</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Tech</Type>
      <Faction>Xindi</Faction>
      <Cost>1</Cost>
      <Id>escape_pod_72004p</Id>
      <Set>72004p</Set>
      <Special></Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Prototype Weapon</Title>
      <Ability>ATTACK: Discard this card and your Captain Card to perform this attack. Place a Mission Token in the play area in your forward firing arc, within Range 1 of your ship that is not on top of another ship's base. Using a 360-degree arc from the Mission Token, target all ships in a line up to Range 2 and make a separate attack against each ship in the line (at -1 attack die for each ship past the first). Remove the Mission Token from the play area after the attack. This Upgrade may only be purchased for a Xindi ship.</Ability>
      <Unique>N</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack>5</Attack>
      <Range>1</Range>
      <Type>Weapon</Type>
      <Faction>Xindi</Faction>
      <Cost>5</Cost>
      <Id>prototype_weapon_72004p</Id>
      <Set>72004p</Set>
      <Special>OnlyXindi</Special>
    </Upgrade>
