    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Neuro Toxin</Title>
      <Ability>If an Upgrade on your ship is affected by an opposing ship, you may discard this card to disable the Captain and every [CREW] Upgrade on the opposing ship.</Ability>
      <Unique>Y</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Talent</Type>
      <Faction>Xindi</Faction>
      <Cost>5</Cost>
      <Id>neuro_toxin_72003p</Id>
      <Set>72003p</Set>
      <Special></Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Phase Deflector Pulse</Title>
      <Ability>If your ship executes a maneuver that would cause its base to overlap another ship's base, after moving your ship backward along the template until it no longer overlaps the other ship, you may discard this card to immediately perform an additional 2 [STRAIGHT] Maneuver. If you do so, you do not lose your "Perform Action" step. This Upgrade may only be purchased for a Xindi ship and no ship may be equipped with more than 1 "Phase Deflector Pulse" Upgrade.</Ability>
      <Unique>N</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Tech</Type>
      <Faction>Xindi</Faction>
      <Cost>5</Cost>
      <Id>phase_deflector_pulse_72003p</Id>
      <Set>72003p</Set>
      <Special>NoMoreThanOnePerShipAndOnlyXindi</Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Insectoid Riflemen</Title>
      <Ability>ACTION: If your ship is not Cloaked, disabled all of your remaining Shields and target a ship at Range 1-2 that is not Cloaked and has no Active Shields. Discard this card to disable all [CREW] Upgrades on the target ship and then place an Auxiliary Power Token beside that ship.</Ability>
      <Unique>N</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Crew</Type>
      <Faction>Xindi</Faction>
      <Cost>5</Cost>
      <Id>insectoid_riflemen_72003p</Id>
      <Set>72003p</Set>
      <Special></Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Pulse-Firing Particle Cannon</Title>
      <Ability>ATTACK: Disable this card to perform this attack. You may only fire this weapon from your forward firing arc. Once per round, if this attack hits, you may immediately make an additional attack with this weapon against the same target with half the attack dice rounded down. This Upgrade costs +5 SP if purchased for a non-Xindi ship.</Ability>
      <Unique>N</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack>3</Attack>
      <Range>1-3</Range>
      <Type>Weapon</Type>
      <Faction>Xindi</Faction>
      <Cost>4</Cost>
      <Id>pulse_firing_particle_cannon_72003p</Id>
      <Set>72003p</Set>
      <Special>Plus5NotXindi</Special>
    </Upgrade>
