    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Salvage</Title>
      <Ability>If a ship is destroyed within Range 1-2 of your ship, you may discard this card and disable all of your Active Shields to steal 1 [TECH] or [WEAPON] Upgrade with a cost of 5 SP or less from that ship even if it exceeds your ship's restrictions. If you do so, place a Disabled Upgrade Token on the stolen Upgrade and place an Auxiliary Power Token beside your ship.</Ability>
      <Unique>Y</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Talent</Type>
      <Faction>Independent</Faction>
      <Cost>4</Cost>
      <Id>salvage_71797</Id>
      <Set>71797</Set>
      <Special></Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Gorn Raiding Party</Title>
      <Ability>ACTION: If your ship is not Cloaked, disable all of your remaining Shields and target a ship at Range 1-2 that is not cloaked. Target ship must disable 2 of its Active Shields, if possible. If the target ship has no Active Shields or if this Action causes the target ship to have no Active Shields, discard this card and disable all Upgrades on the target ship.</Ability>
      <Unique>Y</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Crew</Type>
      <Faction>Independent</Faction>
      <Cost>5</Cost>
      <Id>gorn_raiding_party_71797</Id>
      <Set>71797</Set>
      <Special></Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Improved Deflector Screens</Title>
      <Ability>When defending, during the Compare Results step, if you have any Active Shields, cancel 1 [HIT] or [CRIT] result. Discard this Upgrade if all of your Shields are destroyed. This Upgrade may only be purchased for a ship with a Hull value of 3 or less and no ship may be equipped with more than one "Improved Deflector Screens" Upgrade.</Ability>
      <Unique>N</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack></Attack>
      <Range></Range>
      <Type>Tech</Type>
      <Faction>Independent</Faction>
      <Cost>4</Cost>
      <Id>improved_deflector_screens_71797</Id>
      <Set>71797</Set>
      <Special>Yes</Special>
    </Upgrade>
    <Upgrade>
      <Title>Targeted Phaser Strike</Title>
      <Ability>ATTACK: Disable this card to perform this attack. In addition to inflicting normal damage, for every [HIT] or [CRIT] result, disable 1 [WEAPON] Upgrade on the target ship (max 2). This Upgrade costs +4 SP for any ship other than a Gorn Raider.</Ability>
      <Unique>N</Unique>
      <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
      <Skill></Skill>
      <Talent></Talent>
      <Attack>4</Attack>
      <Range>1-3</Range>
      <Type>Weapon</Type>
      <Faction>Independent</Faction>
      <Cost>4</Cost>
      <Id>targeted_phaser_strike_71797</Id>
      <Set>71797</Set>
      <Special>Yes</Special>
    </Upgrade>
