  <Captain>
    <Title>Bioship Beta Pilot</Title>
    <Ability>When attacking, during the Modify Attack Dice step, you may re-roll 1 of your blank results. If your ship was just destroyed and another friendly ship is within Range 1-2 of your ship, you may replace that ship's Captain Card with this card. If this Captain fielded an [ELITE TALENT] Upgrade, you may assign that Upgrade to the new ship as well, if possible.</Ability>
    <Unique>Y</Unique>
    <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
    <Skill>8</Skill>
    <Talent>1</Talent>
    <Attack></Attack>
    <Range></Range>
    <Type>Captain</Type>
    <Faction>Species 8472</Faction>
    <Cost>6</Cost>
    <Id>bioship_beta_pilot_72012</Id>
    <Set>72012</Set>
    <Special></Special>
  </Captain>
  <Captain>
    <Title>Quark</Title>
    <Ability>ACTION: Discard all of your Upgrades to target a ship at Range 1-2. Target ship cannot attack your ship this round. You must discard at least 1 Upgrade to use this Action. You cannot attack or perform any free Actions this round.</Ability>
    <Unique>Y</Unique>
    <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
    <Skill>3</Skill>
    <Talent>1</Talent>
    <Attack></Attack>
    <Range></Range>
    <Type>Captain</Type>
    <Faction>Ferengi</Faction>
    <Cost>2</Cost>
    <Id>quark_72013</Id>
    <Set>72013</Set>
    <Special></Special>
  </Captain>
  <Captain>
    <Title>Brunt</Title>
    <Ability>ACTION: When defending this round, during the Modify Attack Dice step, you may force 1 opposing ship to re-roll 1 of its attack dice (your choice). You may field the Grand Nagus [ELITE TALENT] Upgrade. If you use the Action listed on it, you must discard this card as well.</Ability>
    <Unique>Y</Unique>
    <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
    <Skill>4</Skill>
    <Talent>0</Talent>
    <Attack></Attack>
    <Range></Range>
    <Type>Captain</Type>
    <Faction>Ferengi</Faction>
    <Cost>3</Cost>
    <Id>brunt_72013</Id>
    <Set>72013</Set>
    <Special>Yes</Special>
  </Captain>
  <Captain>
    <Title>Zek</Title>
    <Ability>ACTION: Target a ship at Range 1. Disable 1 of your Upgrades and 1 Upgrade (your choice) on the target ship. This card may only be purchased for a Ferengi ship.</Ability>
    <Unique>Y</Unique>
    <MirrorUniverseUnique>N</MirrorUniverseUnique>
    <Skill>2</Skill>
    <Talent>1</Talent>
    <Attack></Attack>
    <Range></Range>
    <Type>Captain</Type>
    <Faction>Ferengi</Faction>
    <Cost>1</Cost>
    <Id>zek_cap_72013</Id>
    <Set>72013</Set>
    <Special>Yes</Special>
    <AdmiralAbility>FLEET ACTION: Target a ship at Range 1. Disable 1 of your Upgrades and 1 Upgrade (your choice) on the target ship. This card may only be purchased for a Ferengi ship.</AdmiralAbility>
    <AdmiralCost>1</AdmiralCost>
    <AdmiralTalent>1</AdmiralTalent>
    <SkillModifier>0</SkillModifier>
  </Captain>
